

EDUCATION

B.E (CSE)

United Institute of Technology 2016

HSC (12th STANDARD)

Devanga Higher Secondary School 2012

SSLC (10th STANDARD)

Devanga Higher Secondary School 2010

CERTIFICATIONS

AI & PS CC

Advanced & Essentials Training Course - UDEMY

Oracle Certification

Java SE 7 Programmer Oracle

Phone

+91 9488056804

Email

mugeshbabu1994@gmail.com

website

behance.net/mugeshbabu

Address

No: 22, New weavers colony, Raja annamalai street, Saibaba colony, Coimbatore - 641011.

MUGESH BABU B

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

ABOUT ME

Professional designer with 6+ years of experience specializing in graphics designing with also administration skills for a small scale based company. My greatest strength is creating attractive designs, which I would like to collaborate with your firm and utilize it efficiently.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017-2020 **GRAPHICS DESIGNER**

Vanguard Exports / Coimbatore, Tamilnadu

2020-2021 **GRAPHICS DESIGNER**

IPSW PRIVATE LIMITED / Coimbatore, Tamilnadu

2021-Present SENIOR GRAPHICS DESIGNER

CHARLES GROUP / Coimbatore, Tamilnadu

JOB DESCRIPTION

- I have ability to prioritize work to meet strict deadlines is a result of possessing strong team and project management skills
- I possess excellent interpersonal skills and am able to work collaboratively with others.
- Manage and coordinate the processes of graphic design, production, and copywriting.
- Develops policies, procedures, and guidelines for creating media content.
- Familiar with the principles of graphic design, color theory, and UX/UI.
- Create and produce creative, high-quality graphically engaging course material in accordance with client/brand specifications, which includes creating design layouts, templates, infographics, PDFs, banners, posters, videos, and animations.
- Knowledge of video editing and content authoring tools such as Camtasia.
- Excellent MS Office skills, analytical skills, and attention to detail.

SOFTWARE SKILL











